polylang.pro 2019-12-10

# Privacy policy – Polylang

WP SYNTEX offers WordPress plugins that allow websites to publish content in multiple language.  
This privacy policy describes the type of personal data that we collect. It also describes how we use the personal data and with whom we share it, your rights and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Payment

When you purchase from us, we ask you to provide information including your name, address, email address, credit card/payment details. We also collect your IP address. We use this information to:

  * Send you information about your account and order
  * Answer to your requests, including refunds and complaints
  * Process payments and prevent fraud
  * Set up your account for our store
  * Comply with any legal obligations that we have, such as calculating taxes

### Contact form

The information submitted through the support form are sent to Helpscout, You can find more about [the privacy policy of Helpscout](https://www.helpscout.net/company/legal/gdpr/).

### Comments

We do not allow comments on any page. Comments left prior to 2018 have all been deleted.

### Cookies

We don’t use analytics, avertizing or social media cookies. But we are using cookies, essential to make our website work:

  * `__stripe_sid`: Cookie from Stripe (one of the payment platform that we use), expires after 30 minutes.
  * `__stripe_mid`: Cookie from Stripe (one of the payment platform that we use), expires after 1 year.
  * `edd_items_in_cart`: Stores how many items you have in the cart, expires after 30 minutes.
  * `PHPSESSID`: Used to establish a user session and to pass state data, expires at the end of the session.
  * `wordpress_logged_in_*`: If you have an account and you log in, this cookie will keep you connected to your account, expires after 2 weeks or when you log out.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.  
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Data shared with our support

All data that you share with our support team is stored in [Helpscout](https://www.helpscout.net/).  
Sometimes, to help our support to debug an issue on your site, we might ask you access to your FTP account of your site backend. We use this access strictly for debugging and do not share any data with anyone outside of the company. We recommend that you reset the passwords once you don’t need our support anymore. We cannot be held responsible for any loss of private information from databases if that should occur. We recommend that you have always a fully working backup of the site you share with us.

### Data collected by our plugins

Polylang or the Polylang addons that we provide to you do not collect any personal data without your users’s consent. Polylang allows your user to translate their biographical info. It is considered as personal data and is [exported with other personal data](https://codex.wordpress.org/Tools_Export_Personal_Data_Screen) of your users.  
Polylang does not send any data from your website to us. Polylang Pro and our other premium plugins collect your domain name an IP address when you activate your licence key. This information is used to enable the automatic updates.

## Who we share your data with

We don’t share your data with third-parties in a way as to reveal any of your personal information except for payments.  
We accept payments through PayPal. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information. Please see the [PayPal privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) for more details.  
We also use Stripe for payment. Stripe collects identifying information about the devices that connect to its services. Stripe uses this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection. You can learn more about [Stripe privacy policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).

## Who can see your personal information

If you are not a registered client in our site, there is no personal information we have or can see about you.  
If you are a customer, your personal information can be accessed by the website’s administrator and the support team when it’s needed to get the information about your account in order to provide support

## How long we retain your data

If you have an account, all personal data that we hold about you were collected for legal reasons. We must keep them at least 10 years.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can’t request that we erase any personal data we hold about you because we are obliged to keep them for legal reasons.

## How we protect your data

We are entirely using SSL/HTTPS throughout all our site. This encrypts our user communications with the servers so personal identifiable information is never captured by third parties without authorization.

## What data breach procedures we have in place

Administrators will immediately go through affected users and will attempt to reset passwords if needed after informing the user. Then we will contact each user that might be affected.

## Your contact information

The website [https://polylang.pro](https://polylang.pro/) is a service offered by :  
WP SYNTEX  
28, rue Jean Sébastien Bach, 38090 Villefontaine, France.  
S.A.R.L with a capital of 10 000€  
RCS : 819 143 645 Vienne  
VAT Number : FR64 819 143 645  
Publication director : Frédéric Demarle  
CNIL Declaration number : 1947430  
Hosting : WP Serveur – 7 rue de la Cité, Foulc, 30000 Nîmes

You can contact us at <https://polylang.pro/support/>

Polylang is a registered trademark.
